# KYLE M. CHAMBERS

Systems IT Analyst

#### Contact

**Address** 

Hoboken, NJ, 07030

**Phone** 

+1 862-579-7933

E-mail

kyle.chambers13@outlook.com

#### **Skills**

Python

Tableau

SQL

HTML/CSS

Microsoft Exchange

SharePoint

PowerShell

My background is in information technology and management and I've worked in several different areas in the industry from Information Security to UI development. I'm amazed by the way data influences critical decision making and strive to learn more about how I could use programming to make positive impacts in my field.

#### **Work History**

2018-01 -Current

#### **Systems Analyst**

Brown Brothers Harriman & Company, Jersey City, NJ Collaboration Engineering & Development - Our team engineers a modern, robust collaborative platform for users and applications on Exchange, SharePoint, Skype for Business

- Migrated 6,000 users from IBM Domino platform to Microsoft Exchange
- Support and develop Exchange products for client facing parties
- Migrated 500 IBM Connections applications to SharePoint Environment

2016-07 -2018-12

#### **IT Analyst**

Brown Brothers Harriman & Company, Jersey City, New Jersey

Two-year rotational program designed to develop business technology professionals out of university.

#### **Education**

2012-08 -2016-05

## Bachelor of Science: Information Technology & Management

Syracuse University - Syracuse, NY
Minor: Global Enterprise Technology
Phanstiel Scholarship in recognition of academic success
with demonstrated leadership.

#### **Accomplishments**

- Created a workflow automation process for new hires to be entered in the Employee Directory
- Created Server Inventory site to manage and request hardware
- Developed daily usage reports for the SharePoint environment
- Supported and tested roll-out of Email Validation tool in DLP effort

### **Additional Information**

My GitHub Page & Profile- https://myfriendkmc.github.io/ My Tableau Public Profile - https://public.tableau.com/profile/kyle.chambers#!/